export const questionL5 = [
    {
      question: '90 / 10',
      choices: ['2', '8', '1', '9'],
      correctAnswer: '9',
    },
    {
      question: '100 / 5',
      choices: ['12', '13', '6', '20'],
      correctAnswer: '20',
    },
    {
      question: '25 * 4',
      choices: ['200', '180', '40', '100'],
      correctAnswer: '100',
    },
    {
      question: '20 * 5',
      choices: ['250', '40', '120', '100'],
      correctAnswer: '100',
    },
    {
      question: '80 * 2',
      choices: ['120', '210', '150', '160'],
      correctAnswer: '160',
    },
    {
      question: '100 * 4',
      choices: ['360', '300', '600', '400'],
      correctAnswer: '400',
    },
    {
      question: '280 / 2',
      choices: ['70', '100', '80', '140'],
      correctAnswer: '140',
    },
    {
      question: '90 / 3',
      choices: ['20', '40', '60', '30'],
      correctAnswer: '30',
    },
    {
      question: '300 / 3',
      choices: ['200', '130', '110', '100'],
      correctAnswer: '100',
    },
    {
      question: '100 / 4',
      choices: ['29', '75', '61', '25'],
      correctAnswer: '25',
    },
    {
        question: '200 / 5',
        choices: ['30', '40', '100', '60'],
        correctAnswer: '400',
      },
      {
        question: '210 / 7',
        choices: ['80', '30', '60', '50'],
        correctAnswer: '30',
      },
      {
        question: '180 / 2',
        choices: ['70', '90', '40', '100'],
        correctAnswer: '90',
      },
      {
        question: '360 / 9',
        choices: ['80', '110', '30', '40'],
        correctAnswer: '40',
      },
      {
        question: '140 * 2',
        choices: ['200', '160', '180', '280'],
        correctAnswer: '280',
      },
      {
        question: '30 * 6',
        choices: ['170', '650', '190', '180'],
        correctAnswer: '180',
      },
      {
        question: '20 * 7',
        choices: ['120', '80', '150', '140'],
        correctAnswer: '140',
      },
      {
        question: '40 * 9',
        choices: ['107', '240', '280', '360'],
        correctAnswer: '360',
      },
      {
        question: '50 * 5',
        choices: ['200', '50', '270', '250'],
        correctAnswer: '250',
      },
      {
        question: '30 * 4',
        choices: ['190', '200', '130', '120'],
        correctAnswer: '120',
      },
      {
        question: '8 / 60',
        choices: ['48', '170', '260', '480'],
        correctAnswer: '480',
      },
      {
        question: '9 * 80',
        choices: ['200', '720', '610', '450'],
        correctAnswer: '720',
      },
      {
        question: '4 / 90',
        choices: ['60', '180', '405', '360'],
        correctAnswer: '360',
      },
      {
        question: '6 * 40',
        choices: ['240', '320', '510', '420'],
        correctAnswer: '240',
      },
      {
        question: '4 * 80',
        choices: ['90', '320', '80', '270'],
        correctAnswer: '320',
      },
      {
          question: '810 / 9',
          choices: ['120', '200', '680', '90'],
          correctAnswer: '90',
        },
        {
          question: '300 / 60',
          choices: ['4', '3', '8', '5'],
          correctAnswer: '5',
        },
        {
          question: '40 * 20',
          choices: ['150', '320', '160', '175'],
          correctAnswer: '160',
        },
        {
          question: '400 / 50',
          choices: ['2', '3', '8', '6'],
          correctAnswer: '8',
        },
        {
          question: '160 / 8',
          choices: ['20', '41', '18', '12'],
          correctAnswer: '20',
        },
  ]
  export default questionL5